The one word I would use to describe my
experience with many life is growth,
learning, transformative, enriching,
incredible.
[Music]
I wanted to work for a company that
cares about the society, cares about the
people. Insurance is about people's
life. Having that social responsibility
in mind is really important. I'm working
in an environment that's really creating
solutions and also values to our
customers. Working for a company that
cares about people means a lot to me. It
makes me feel included and happier. I
participated in the company investor day
which is one of the highest level events
in the company. I was given the
opportunity to meet the investors and
showcase our penny life strength. What
surprised me by men life is the
flexibility and opportunities to explore
as a junior back then. I think the best
part working in my team is the openness
to new ideas and feedback. It just
empowers me a lot uh by uh working in
this environment. I truly believe in uh
what our companies believe in. I'm sure
the technical skills and the
foundational values that I'm learning at
Manolife would really help me in the
future of my career because these are
the skills I would continuously use as
my career progresses. I had the
opportunity to participate in hack
giving hackathon. Together we work on a
project to solve some business problems.
If you ever been to the floor, you'll
know it's a very inclusive, kind
environment to work in. You feel that
you're connected to every team member.
My manager cares about my well-being and
cares about my career development. This
really makes me feel this is a good role
and also a job that I really want to be
in in the future.
[Music]